affbuzzads.com 2013-02-10

# CinemaDen.com - Watch movies instantly online

### Privacy Policy

#### Effective Date: July 17, 2012

IMOVIES Ltd. ("CinemaDen", "us", "our" or "we") has developed this Privacy Policy which details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information collected on the website CinemaDen.com, which is owned and operated by CinemaDen and any successor websites (the "Site"), and other interactive properties, including but not limited to any mobile applications (the Site and other CinemaDen interactive properties are collectively referred to herein as the CinemaDen Applications"). CinemaDen provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use, continue to use the services assessed through the CinemaDen Applications ("Services"). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to CinemaDen's Terms of Use: <https://www.cinemaden.com/terms>. Each time that you access or use CinemaDen Applications you signify that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by the Terms of Use, and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue using the CinemaDen Applications.

#### I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### Connecting with the CinemaDen Applications and Information Provided by You

**Contacting Us.** When you provide us with information in connection with a particular activity or otherwise sign up for our services or provide your contact information, including an email address or telephone number in connection with that activity, product or service, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase or inquiry establishing a business relationship with us. You expressly consent to our communicating with you future information about CinemaDen using the information you provided to us. You also attest that you have the legal authority over any telephone number you provide to us and can provide us with the authorization to contact you. This means we may contact you, in person or by recorded message, by e-mail, telephone and/or mobile telephone number (including use of automated dialing equipment), text (SMS) message, or any other means of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving.

**Registration Information.** We will collect personal information from you when you register for any CinemaDen membership, interact with our CinemaDen Applications update your profile, interact with other users, and use various features of our CinemaDen Applications. By signing up, you give us permission to store and display user information you have provided in order to provide the best possible experience on the CinemaDen Applications.

**Billing Information.** We collect and store billing and credit card information. This information will only be shared with third parties who perform tasks required to complete the purchase transaction. Examples of this include fulfilling orders and processing credit/debit cards.

**Surveys and Promotions.** From time-to-time we may request information from you and other users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary so you and other users have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Survey information will be used for the purpose(s) of the survey, including the monitoring or improvement of the use and satisfaction of CinemaDen Applications.

**User Generated Content.** Please remember that any information you disclose while participating on the public e-mail services, chat areas and/or other message, communication or other interactive forums accessed through the CinemaDen Applications which are designed to enable you to communicate with others or to post content on the Sites ("Communication Services"), becomes public information, becomes the property of, and is subject to redistribution by, CinemaDen. You should exercise caution and discretion when deciding to disclose your personal information in a submission or posting. There is no expectation of privacy when playing, posting, or otherwise participating on the Communication Services. If you post content, such as messages, photos and videos, please be aware that any personally identifiable information contained in such content is accessible to registered users or visitors to that CinemaDen Application or Communication Service and we have no control over how those users may use your personally identifiable information. We have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any activity and content associated with the Communication Services. We reserve the right to take action in connection with any content we deem to be inappropriate. Please review our Terms of Use for more information regarding your appropriate use of these areas.

#### Information Collected Through Technology

In addition to any personal information or other information that you choose to submit to us, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the CinemaDen Applications ("Usage Information"). This may include the browser that you are using, the URL that referred you to the CinemaDen Applications, all of the areas within the CinemaDen Applications that you visit, and the time of day, among other information. We may use the this Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including to enhance or otherwise improve the CinemaDen Applications. In addition, we collect your IP address or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier") for your computer or other device used to access the CinemaDen Applications (any, a "Device"). A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to the device used to access the CinemaDen Applications, and our computers identify your device by its Device Identifier. Usage Information may be non-identifying or may be associated with you. Whenever we associate Usage Information or a Device Identifier with your personal information, we will treat it as personal information.   
A few of the tracking technologies that may be used to collect Usage Information include, without limitation, the following:

**Cookies.** A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Site. We use cookies to collect information for record keeping purposes, to make it easier to navigate the Site. Cookies are stored on users' hard drives. We use both "session ID cookies" and "persistent cookies." Session ID cookies are used to store information while a user is logged into the Site and expire when the user closes his/her browser. Persistent cookies are used to make tasks like logging into the Site easier for returning users by remembering a user's login information. Persistent cookies stay on a user's hard drive from one session to the next. Flash cookies, known as local shared objects, are data files placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device to personalize your visit. Our third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from standard browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences and tracking your visits to our web pages. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a persistent or session cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off such cookies through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. However, cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html. If you choose to disable cookies on your Device, some features of the Site may not function properly.

**Web Beacons.** Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as "1x1 GIFs" or "clear GIFs") may be included in our web pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to our Sites, to monitor how users navigate the Sites, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

**Embedded Scripts.** An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the CinemaDen Applications, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Sites, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

**HTML5.** We use HTML5 in the CinemaDen Applications and mobile website for the iphone or ipad (and any other Apple iOS device). HTML5 has browser web storage that does not rely on traditional browser cookies. Like Flash cookies, HTML5 cookies are not stored in a browser "cookies" file and, like Flash cookies, can be used to track users across websites. To our knowledge there is currently no known way for a user of a mobile device to remove HTML5 tracking and storage.

**Web Logs.** Like most standard website servers, we log IP addresses (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) and device identification in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the CinemaDen Applications. We may track your movement within the CinemaDen Applications, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types. This information may include the browser you are using, the Internet address from which you linked to our CinemaDen Applications, the operating system of your computer, the unique IP address of the computer or device identification from the mobile device that you used to access our CinemaDen Applications and usage and browsing habits. We use this information in the aggregate to gauge the effectiveness, usage, and popularity of our CinemaDen Applications, track information for statistical purposes, help diagnose and troubleshoot server malfunctions, analyze trends, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. We may also use individual information we collect through web logs to send you targeted offers and other communications.

#### Information You Provide About a Third Party

If you send someone else a communication from the CinemaDen Applications, such as sending an invitation to a friend, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. If that person becomes a subscriber to our publications, his/her information will be treated in the same manner as all other subscribers. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on the CinemaDen Applications, your e-mail address may be included in the communication sent to your friend.

#### Information We Collect From Third Parties

We acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information you provided or we collected automatically, such as information to validate or update your address or other demographic and lifestyle information. We use this information to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect, to target our communications so that we can inform you of products, services and offers that may be of interest, and for internal business analysis or other business purposes.

#### Third Party Analytics Technologies

We use third parties' analytic tools, provided by Google Analytics, to better understand who is using the Site, how people are using the Site and how to improve the effectiveness of the Site and its content. Those third party companies may use cookies, pixel tags or other technologies to collect and store anonymous information such as time of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the Site, Device Identifiers, type of operating system used and other web sites you may have visited. We do not have access to, nor control over, Google's use of cookies or other tracking technologies. If you would like more information regarding Google's use of cookies or other tracking tools on our Site or want to know more about your choices about not having this anonymous collected or used, please click here. [ https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

#### Third Party Advertising

We also use third-party ad servers and ad networks to serve advertisements when you visit the CinemaDen Applications. These companies and the advertisers themselves may use information about your visits on other web sites and CinemaDen Applications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to CinemaDen Applications, these third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your Device, the advertisements and links that appear on the CinemaDen Applications. They automatically receive your Device Identifier when this happens. They may also use tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers, ad servers or ad networks. You should consult the respective privacy policies of any advertisers on our CinemaDen Applications to see your options for opting out of their use of such devices. In addition, some of the ad servers and ad networks may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. If you opt-out of receiving targeted ads on our CinemaDen Applications from ad servers and ad networks, you will continue to receive advertising and promotional messages after you opt-out, but they will not be customized or personalized to you based on your use of our CinemaDen Applications and/or third party web sites. If you would like more information about advertisers' use of tracking technologies and about your option not to accept these cookies, you can go to www.networkadvertising.org . If you would like to learn more about how interest-based information is collected, whether the companies we use are part of an industry network regarding behavioral advertising and to know your choices about not having information used in this manner you can go to www.aboutads.info .

Our Ads on Third Party Sites. We may use information collected using third party cookies and Web beacons on CinemaDen Applications and in our emails to deliver advertising about our Services displayed to you on third party websites. We also may use cookies to collect information to know when you return to our CinemaDen Applications after visiting those third party websites. We use this information and other information about you, to try to understand your interests and show you relevant advertising about our Services which you might be interested in. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, ad servers or ad networks we use to display our ads on other websites. Some of the ad servers and ad networks we use to display our ads may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. If you would like more information about advertisers' use of tracking technologies and about your option not to accept these cookies you can go to www.networkadvertising.org . If you would like to learn more about how interest-based information is collected to serve advertising on the internet you can go to www.aboutads.info .

#### II. HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

**Use of Information by Us.** We may use Information that we collect about you: 

  * (1) to provide you with information or services or process transactions that you have requested or agreed to receive; 
  * (2) to provide you with information regarding new features, products or services;
  * (3) to improve the CinemaDen Applications or our Services and to customize your experience; 
  * (4) to contact you with regard to your use of the Site and, in our discretion, changes to the Site and/or the Site's policies;
  * (5) for internal business purposes;
  * (6) to share with our marketing partners; and
  * (7) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Transactional Communications.** We may send you notices from time to time relating to your account or your subscriptions. These may include order confirmations, renewal notices, invoices or customer service notifications. We may also send you service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so; for instance, if our Service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, or the delivery of a product is delayed or there is some service issue with something you may have ordered. You may not opt-out of receiving these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

**Service Providers.** We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the CinemaDen Applications or administer activities on our behalf. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.

**Promotional Offers.** We may send you promotional emails regarding special offers about our publications or on behalf of third party marketing partners who we think can offer services and products of interest to you and/or share your name and email address and certain other information, such as when you first subscribed, with reputable companies that provide marketing offers electronically or through postal mail. If you do not want to receive emails regarding special promotions or offers, or have your information shared with third parties you may 

  * (i) Update your email preference Settings by visiting <https://www.cinemaden.com/members>, clicking the "My Account", then click the "Preferences" tab and uncheck the unwanted email subscriptions, or 
  * (ii) Click the unsubscribe link in the body of the email.

Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional emails or direct mail offers, we may continue to send you service notifications that are related to your account(s) and other products and services you have requested or in which you are currently enrolled.

**Co-branded Areas.** Certain areas on our CinemaDen Applications may be provided to you in association with third parties such as sponsors or advertisers ("Co-Branded Areas") and may request that you disclose personal information to them. Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party. If you elect to register for products and/or services at Co-Branded Areas, you may be providing your information to both us and the third party. Your personal information will be subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the privacy policy and practices of such third party. We are not responsible for the privacy policy of practices of such third party. You should consult the respective privacy policies of those third party sponsors or advertisers to learn more about their privacy practices.

**Legal Matters; Safety.** We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you (including, without limitation, the contents of any chat, messaging, or other communication posted in the Communication Services), and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law (including, but not limited to, court order or subpoena), or to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Use or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Additionally, we may disclose your information and/or communications in situations that we believe to be: 

  * (i) emergencies involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property if we believe that your information in any way relates to that threat; or 
  * (ii) your conduct on the CinemaDen Applications or when using the Communication Services that we believe is inappropriate and inconsistent with generally accepted norms of behavior.

**Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets.** In the event that we, or any of our businesses, are sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, personally identifiable information of our visitors may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. Information about our visitors and registered users may also need to be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where we or any one of our businesses are seeking financing, investment, support or funding. In such transactions, personal information will be subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy in effect when the information was obtained.

#### III. ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

If you have an online account with us, you also may choose to resign and deactivate your account at any time. Please visit (<https://www.cinemaden.com/support//front/cancel>) for removal information for your particular product. After you close your account, you will not be able to sign in to our CinemaDen Applications or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new, separate account at any time or re-activate your previous account by logging in again. If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information you provided to us is not correct and you cannot change it by accessing your account, or should you wish to have your email address removed from our mailing list or contact information changed, please contact us at [privacy@CinemaDen.com](mailto:privacy@CinemaDen.com). We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. If you deactivate your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, enforce our Terms of Use or other policies, take actions we deem necessary due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our CinemaDen Applications. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes and enforce our Terms of Use.

#### IV. CHOICE AND OPT OUT

You may remove your information from our database so as not to receive future communications or to close your account or opt out of our sharing information with third parties for marketing purposes by emailing us at [privacy@CinemaDen.com](mailto:privacy@CinemaDen.com) or sending snail mail (certified mail, return receipt requested is recommended) to the following address:

iMovies Ltd.  
483 GREEN LANES  
LONDON  
N13 4BS  
United Kingdom  
Attention: Privacy 

If you prefer not to receive electronic promotional communications, you can opt-out by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each communication.

Please note that changes may not be effective immediately. In each event, you must clearly indicate the information that you wish to have changed or clearly indicate that you wish to have your personally identifiable information removed from our database. We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably possible. Note that despite any request for removal of or change to personally identifiable information, we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and there may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed or changed. Finally, we are not responsible for informing third parties (including without limitation our third party service providers or strategic partners) with whom we have already shared your personally identifiable information of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities.

**Your California Privacy Rights (As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83)**

California's "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the business' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. We have such a policy in place. If you do not want us to send you emails regarding special promotions or offers or share your Personal Information with other companies so that they can send you emails about their products and services, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions that are located at the bottom of those emails or you can Update your email preference Settings by visiting <https://www.cinemaden.com/members>, clicking the "My Account", then click the "Preferences" tab and uncheck the sharing of information to third parties, or (ii) Click the unsubscribe link in the body of the email. If you do not want us to send you any offers from third parties through direct mail or share your Personal Information with other companies so that they can send you direct mail offers about their products and services, please write to us at the street address set forth at the end of this document email us a privacy@CinemaDen.com. California customers may request further information about our approach to this law by writing to us at the addresses provided.

#### V. IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES, PRACTICES AND CONTACT INFORMATION

**Links to other Site and Communities.** To the extent hyperlinks may be utilized to access external or third party sites and communities, you should be aware that these external or third party site and communities are not controlled by us and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of each such site and community to determine how your personal information will be utilized by their proprietors.

**Security.** We implement safeguards to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. However, despite our efforts, no data transmission over the Internet, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and your use of the Site indicates that you are willing to assume this risk.

**A Note To International Users.** If you are located anywhere outside of Barbados, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to, processed and stored in and outside Barbados. The data protection laws in Barbados may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in Barbados according to laws of Barbados. By using the CinemaDen Applications or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in Barbados. You are also consenting to the application of Barbados law in all matters concerning the Site and this Privacy Policy.

**Children's Privacy.** The CinemaDen Applications are not directed or intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from individuals under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not register or provide Personal Information on the CinemaDen Applications. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 13 years of age, we will take steps to remove that user's Personal Information from our systems.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy.** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on our Sites, with the "Effective Date" posted at the top of the Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new CinemaDen Applications or Community Services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information, you will know because the Effective Date of the Privacy Policy will change. If we are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your personal information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time we obtained that information. By accessing the CinemaDen Applications after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. We will use information previously obtained in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

**Disputes.** If you choose to visit the CinemaDen Applications your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of Barbados.

**No Rights of Third Parties.** This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

**Contacting Us.** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of the CinemaDen Applications and Community Services, please send your email queries to [privacy@CinemaDen.com](mailto:privacy@CinemaDen.com) or write to us at:

iMovies Ltd.  
483 GREEN LANES  
LONDON  
N13 4BS  
United Kingdom  
Attention: Privacy Administrator 

Copyright (c) 2013 IMOVIES Ltd. All rights reserved.

Go up »
